<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".MainActivity">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView2"
        android:layout_width="335dp"
        android:layout_height="43dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="32dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="32dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="32dp"
        android:text="Vegeta"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_width="339dp"
        android:layout_height="42dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
        android:text="Prince of Sayajins"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="@+id/textView2"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="@+id/textView2"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/textView2" />

    <ScrollView
        style="@android:style/Widget.ScrollView"
        android:layout_width="340dp"
        android:layout_height="476dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="@+id/textView"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.0"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="@+id/textView"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/textView"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Regal, egotistical, and full of pride, Vegeta was once a ruthless, cold-blooded warrior and outright killer, but later abandons his role in the Frieza Force, instead opting to remain and live on Earth. His character evolves from villain, to anti-hero, then to hero through the course of the series, repeatedly fighting alongside the universe's most powerful warriors in order to protect his new home and surpass Goku in power. Vegeta is a slim yet very well-built man of a below-average stature, standing at 164 centimeters tall. His hair is black (or dark brown, depending on the media) and spikes upwards. Vegeta has a prominent widow's peak. Like most Saiyans, he possesses defined eyes with a consistently stern look to them. Like other Universe 7 Saiyans, he was born with a prehensile brown-furred tail, until it was permanently cut off by Yajirobe.  Over the course of the series, Vegeta's physical appearance changes. While originally appearing very short and lean, especially compared to his massive partner, Nappa, he later seems to be somewhat taller and noticeably more muscular. His hair and forehead appears to be shorter and his facial features, which are perpetually in a scowl, also look more distinct and sharply defined as the series progresses, making him look much older in later sagas compared to what he looked like in his debut. A major characteristic of Vegeta's is the fact that he is one of the only Saiyans who have continued to don the traditional Saiyan armor in combat. His general look is a dark blue, full-bodied jumpsuit with white gloves and boots with the said armor on top. He has also been seen wearing alternate forms of the armor, customizing it to better suit his persona. When first arriving on Earth, he wore a white armor with yellow shoulder pads and also padding at his hips and groin. Along with it, he wore a red-lens scouter on his left eye. During the Frieza Saga, he replaced his heavily damaged armor with a similar one, minus the padding around his waistline. He also briefly wore another scouter until deeming it unnecessary and destroying it. When his armor was damaged in battle against Recoome, he replaced his outfit with an older model design consisting of a black bodysuit, white gloves and boots, and a near-purely white armor without shoulder pads. In the Trunks Saga, he wore a pink short sleeved loose button shirt with the sign &quot;Bad Man&quot; at the back, a white sleeveless undershirt, yellow pants and green shoes with a brown trim. During the Androids Saga, he wore an updated version of his original armor, but without pads. During the Buu Saga, to be allowed to fight in the World Martial Arts Tournament, Vegeta sported a sleeveless blue bodysuit with white gloves and boots. He later wore this outfit during his sparring match against Goku in Dragon Ball Super: Broly as the color of his bodysuit is blue gray/navy blue.">

        </TextView>

    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>